hi spring fans in this installment of
嗨，春季粉丝在本期中
spring tips we want to take a look at
我们想看看的春季提示
not one particular project and that one
不是一个特定的项目，而那个
particular sort of concern we're going
我们要特别关注的问题
to look at some of the various utility
看一下各种实用程序
classes inside of the spring framework
Spring Framework 内部的类
instead of spring proper these are not
而不是春天，这些不是
to do with any one particular thing as
与任何一件特定的事情有关
well as you'll see we're going to go
就像您看到的那样，我们要走了
through a lot of different sort of use
通过很多不同的用途
cases today I want to just surface some
今天的案例我只想浮出水面
of these because if you're using spring
这些，因为如果您使用弹簧
and you want to take advantage of some
而你想利用一些
of this functionality it's already is
这个功能已经是
there you don't need to reach for
那里你不需要伸手去拿
another library if you don't need it and
如果您不需要另一个库，并且
it may well be that the functionality
很有可能是功能
means already in one Ds utility classes
意味着已经在一个Ds实用程序类中
now that is not to say that you
现在不是说你
shouldn't use other libraries if they
如果其他库不应该使用
meet your use case but I feel like
满足您的用例，但我觉得
surfacing some of these some of these
堆砌其中一些
utility classes could be very useful now
实用程序类现在可能非常有用
we're going to look at all of this in
我们将在其中研究所有这些
terms of very simple in just a strawman
只是在稻草人中非常简单的术语
sort of example so I'll build a new
这样的例子，所以我将建立一个新的
example here we're going to call this to
这里的例子，我们将其称为
be you'll to utility application I'll
是你会去实用程序应用程序
give it a name util examples right and
给它起一个util例子名称，
I'm only going to bring in Lombok which
我只带龙目岛
is the Java annotation processor and for
是Java注释处理器，用于
compile compile time meditation
编译时的冥想
processor will bring in the web support
处理器将带来Web支持
because I'm going to build a web
因为我要建立一个网站
application later we'll bring an AOP
申请后，我们将带来一个AOP
support because we're using that we'll
支持，因为我们正在使用它，我们将
look at a spec Jane and proxy and then I
看看规格简和代理，然后我
think ought to do it and again you know
想应该去做，你又知道
I'm just doing this for that we have
我这样做是为了
something with which to click which to
要点击的东西
play into exercise right so we're not
锻炼身体，所以我们不是
trying to but the goal is not to look at
试图但目的不是看
how to build a web application today
今天如何构建Web应用程序
it's to to look at some of the utility
是要看一些实用程序
classes ok now the first thing we're
上课好了，我们第一件事
going to look at is how spring packages
要看的是春季包装如何
utility classes how do we write that
实用程序类我们该怎么写
code and the the the pattern is fairly
代码和模式是相当
consistent right if you look at a class
如果您上课，一贯的权利
like being utils right here's the Spring
就像成为utils一样，这里是春天
Framework implementation of a type
类型的框架实现
called binutils being utils is a class
叫做binutils是utils是一个类
that we have on the craft path I
我们在工艺路线上
predicted the source code here it says
在这里预测了源代码
that the class is
那班是
abstract right so the class can't be
抽象的权利，所以该类不能
instantiated you're not expected to
实例化您不期望
create any instances of this there's no
创建这个的任何实例
state and then otherwise the methods are
状态，然后方法是
are static now we do where we feel this
现在是静态的，我们在感觉到的地方做
appropriate signal that some of these
适当的信号表明其中一些
methods are for framework use only so
方法仅用于框架，因此
you you do well to look at the Java Docs
您可以很好地查看Java文档
for this for these different utility
对于这些不同的实用程序
classes a lot of them are sort of common
他们很多班很普通
enough and they've been used and in the
足够，它们已经被使用，并且在
framework for long enough that they're
足够长的时间框架
stable and to can benefit from them
稳定并可以从中受益
certainly as stables and other library
当然可以作为马s和其他图书馆
out there but keep in mind that we do
但请记住，我们会
either provide to change so many things
要么提供改变很多事情
and you'll see that pretty clearly sort
然后您会清楚地看到排序
of staked out in the Java documentation
Java文档中放样的
right so when you want to create only a
对，所以当您只想创建一个
study class you can consider this
学习班你可以考虑一下
pattern make it abstract and then put
模式使其抽象，然后放入
you know create static utility methods
你知道创建静态实用程序方法
the value of this is that there's no
它的价值在于没有
side effects there's no state and if
副作用没有状态，如果
there's States and it's explicitly you
有国家，明确地是你
know a singleton static kind of variable
知道单例静态变量
hi all right now let's take a look at
大家好，现在让我们来看看
our example here we've got a utility
我们的示例在这里，我们有一个实用程序
example application and we're going to
示例应用程序，我们将
build a class just a simple class that
建立一个类只是一个简单的类
is a command line runner that we're
是我们的命令行运行者
going to have a beam of a commit command
将有一束提交命令
winner and the Commandant weather's
冠军和指挥官的天气
going to be insensitive in the
会变得不敏感
application starts up and we're going to
应用程序启动，我们将
manage a particular class that have a
管理一个具有
simple strawman class so we have
简单的稻草人课，所以我们有
something with which to work so we're to
与之一起工作的东西，所以我们要
create a class called a demo class and I
创建一个称为演示类的类，然后我
know who cares really it's going to be a
知道谁真的在乎这将是一个
component or spring you know so spring
您知道的弹簧元件或弹簧
me next let's make it the ones making a
接下来，让我们将其制作成
data class because it'll be a long buck
数据类，因为这将是长期的损失
type we want to create a all argument
我们要创建一个all参数的类型
constructor so okay a constructor for
好的构造函数
that and I want to have one field so
那我想有一个领域
that we can reflectively work with that
我们可以反思地与之合作
for later on so okay teh field here
待会儿再来
private final list of map of string of
的字符串映射的私有最终列表
object okay and we want to call this oh
对象好吧，我们要称呼这个哦
it's a list here we're just going to
这是我们要去的清单
call this our list
称之为我们的清单
and we don't really I don't have
而且我们真的没有我没有
anything particularly you know I don't
尤其是你知道我不知道的任何事情
have anything in particular in mind when
有什么特别的想法
I
一世
then steal those want to have something
然后偷那些想要的东西
with lots of generic parameters right a
有很多通用参数
generic type and this is going to be a
通用类型，这将是一个
private final field but because we using
私有最终字段，但是因为我们使用
this Lombok Java imitation processor
这个Lombok Java模仿处理器
will have the ability to call get list
将能够调用获取列表
and set lists on this class it's a it's
并在这个类上设置列表是
a components a job it's a job javabean
一个组件是一个工作，它是一个工作javabean
property sort of could an instance of
属性的种类可以是
that beam will say demo class demo
那个光束会说演示课演示
class or just return new demo class like
课或只返回新的演示课，例如
so and there we are there's our simple
所以那里就是我们的简单
instance or simple beam we've done
我们已经完成的实例或简单光束
precisely nothing to it we're just going
没什么，我们只是去
to inject it there and we can use it now
注入那里，我们现在可以使用它
you know there's a lot of things we can
你知道我们可以做很多事情
do here there's a lot of different
在这里做很多事情
things that you can imagine wanting to
你可以想像的东西
do with a simple thing like this
这样简单的事情
maybe I want to maybe I want to confirm
也许我想也许我想确认
that the property list is not knowable
该属性列表未知
right so already we can see a use case
对，所以我们已经可以看到一个用例
for one of the very convenient utility
对于非常方便的实用程序之一
ties there that are in the spring
春天的联系
firming itself the assert class the
坚定自己的断言阶级
assert class has a bunch of methods sort
断言类有很多方法
of like what you find in in getting it
就像您在获得它时所发现的
to to verify or to assert the state of
验证或断言状态
you know fields objects whatever before
你知道领域对象之前
you operate on them this is you know the
您对他们进行操作，这是您知道的
design my contract I were trying to put
设计我想要的合同
forward some preconditions and assert
提出一些前提条件并断言
those preconditions are true
这些前提是正确的
before we operated them on them this
在我们对他们进行操作之前
makes the code that follows much much
使后面的代码很多
more reasonable right you can understand
您可以理解的更合理的权利
that certain conditions are already - in
某些条件已经存在
order to do or you can build to proceed
命令执行，或者您可以进行构建
to that line right so let's say that
在那条线右边，所以我们说
this field has to be there so we'll say
这个领域必须在那里，所以我们会说
demo doesn't get list right the list
演示没有正确的列表
can't be known right so there's our
不能被正确知道，所以有我们
first example right let's go ahead and
第一个示例正确吧，让我们继续前进，
run this and we'll see that the
运行这个，我们会看到
application spins up we should be able
应用程序旋转起来，我们应该能够
to see the results be you know be okay
看看结果就可以了
now let's change this one it will call a
现在让我们更改此名称，它将称为
setter on our honor oh it's a final
传承我们的荣誉，哦，这是最终决定
variable so let's make its non final so
变量，所以让它成为非最终的
that the compile time process will code
编译时过程将进行编码
generate a set list let's call null okay
生成一个设置列表，让我们称它为null吧
now we should see
现在我们应该看到
that when we rerun this it's going to
当我们重新运行它时，
throw an exception and that exception by
抛出一个异常，该异常由
the way as an illegal argument exception
作为非法论证例外的方式
so you'll get that for free now let's
所以您现在可以免费获得它，让我们
see here
看这里
we wanted no argument constructor as
我们不需要参数构造函数
well right so no argument constructor we
好吧，所以我们没有参数构造函数
learn that code there we are so in that
在那边学习代码，
application starts up it says little
应用程序启动它说很少
arguments to exceptional if campaign
竞选活动的特殊论点
also any code that follows that
以及随后的任何代码
assertion must be true you don't need to
断言必须是真实的，您不需要
you don't need to litter all the code
您不需要乱扔所有代码
with a you know get if no checks and all
与你知道如果没有检查和所有
that stuff and the compiler won't even
这些东西，编译器甚至都不会
warn you about it because it'll know
警告您，因为它会知道
that you know that is cool for you there
你知道那对你很酷
right so that's one convenient I believe
对，所以我认为这是一种方便
this all the time it's used in the
一直在用
spring framework itself all the time
Spring Framework本身一直
right anywhere we want to exert the
在我们想要发挥作用的任何地方
state of an object or to verify certain
对象的状态或验证某些
preconditions we do so with the various
前提是我们对各种
methods on the assert class here so
断言类的方法在这里
there's a method here for checking the
这里有一种方法可以检查
words we're checking whether an instance
我们正在检查一个实例的单词
of an object is assignable to a certain
的对象可分配给某个对象
type checking to see if it's in all to
进行检查以查看是否全部
see if the element of a collection role
查看集合角色的元素
to see if an object or a map or an array
查看对象，地图或数组
are empty to see if an expression in
为空以查看是否包含表达式
general is true to see if text is within
一般是否正确，以查看文本是否在其中
another text to see if text is empty or
另一个文本以查看文本是否为空或
not that lets say whether there's a
不是说，是否有一个
value there you know lots of very very
珍惜那里，你知道很多非常非常
convenient methods here and that's what
这里方便的方法就是这样
there's just a near one called state so
几乎只有一个叫状态
let's just take the boolean and a
让我们只用布尔值和
message of the state is false and it
状态消息是错误的，它
gets you the message right so you can
为您传达正确的信息，以便您可以
you can use these as you like there I
你可以在那里随意使用它们
think you're going to find that they're
以为你会发现他们是
pretty darn convenient now once I've got
一旦我有了，现在很方便
my my bean I would mind
我的豆我会介意的
you know inspecting I maybe I want to
你知道检查我也许我想
look at the properties on that being
看看那个存在的属性
right it's a it's a Java mean after all
对，这毕竟是Java的意思
it's got juggling properties it's going
它具有杂耍特性
to have a getter for this this property
这个属性有一个吸气剂
after all so let's let's look at that
毕竟，让我们来看一下
let's create a method here called beans
让我们在这里创建一个称为bean的方法
and in the beans method will enumerate
并且在bean方法中将枚举
the the property descriptors in the
中的属性描述符
application in the in the bean rather so
在bean中的应用相当
we're going to say that this is going to
我们要说的是
take a demo
进行演示
class demo and we'll put this in here
课堂演示，我们将其放在这里
demo and there we can say a property or
演示，在那里我们可以说一个财产或
started out being utils get property
开始是utils获取属性
descriptors demo dot good class and this
描述符演示点好类和这个
gives me a collection of property
给我一些财产
descriptors that we can then use so I
然后我们可以使用的描述符
can say for property descriptor PD
可以说属性描述符PD
descriptors and let's log n so private
描述符，让我们如此私密地登录
static final log uncle's log sector e
静态最终日志叔叔的日志扇区e
get log you tilt example application
获取日志倾斜示例应用程序
okay there are so we're going to say
好吧，所以我们要说
this dot log R Sloan info PD dot get
该点日志R Sloan信息PD点得到
name alright so we should see for that
好的名字，所以我们应该看到
one type a collection of different
一种类型，不同的集合
properties automatically being captured
自动捕获的属性
to us right so let's see what that looks
对我们来说，让我们看看它的外观
like if we learn the code here being
就像我们在这里学习代码一样
it's already defined demo class what
已经定义了演示类了
have we got hurt all your constructor
我们伤害了你所有的建设者
okay so when I run this I get the the
好吧，所以当我运行这个我得到
following properties they get or the
他们获得以下属性或
property that I can access called class
我可以访问的属性称为类
obviously refers to get class and then
显然是指上课，然后
there's a property called lists and so
有一个叫做列表的属性，所以
you know these are the javabean property
你知道这些是javabean属性
description so I can actually you know
说明，以便我实际上您可以知道
let's see PD okay PD dot get a lead
让我们来看PD正常PD点取得领先
method for example equals get reed
例如等于等于簧片的方法
method ducted name right we don't we
方法管道名称正确，我们不是
know that in this case the interesting
知道在这种情况下，有趣的是
methods of the interesting properties on
有趣特性的方法
the jumping that would look inspecting
看起来很有趣的跳跃
right now don't have any writer right
现在没有任何作家对
methods so we won't bother asking for it
方法，这样我们就不用麻烦了
but you could you could test that for
但是你可以测试一下
example so here the class of the
例子，所以这里的类
properties called class and the leave
属性称为class和leave
method is called get list and get class
该方法称为获取列表和获取类
in that would handle that would hand you
在那会处理你
back a a reference to the Java
返回对Java的引用
reflection method object I okay very
反射方法对象，我很好
good so we have a there with the beam
好，所以我们有一个光束
utils and that beam util gives you a
utils，该梁utils为您提供了
whole bunch of different uh sort of
一大堆不同的呃
convenience methods to copy properties
复制属性的便捷方法
from one object to another to find a
从一个物体到另一个寻找一个
property within being of a certain types
属于某种类型的财产
and stant eight an object based on a
并根据对象固定八个对象
class to you know just generally answer
你知道的课程只是一般的答案
some very common questions this is very
一些非常常见的问题，这是非常
similar I think to some of the types of
我认为与某些类型的
sort of functionality you might find in
您可能会发现的某种功能
the common blank being utils typewriter
常见空白是utils打字机
which has been around forever
一直存在
and if you want to use that that's fine
如果你想使用那很好
but there's a lot of the common things
但是有很多共同点
you're going to need our here and being
你将需要我们在这里
details as well alright so there's one
细节还好，所以有一个
thing I can imagine wanting to do now
我想现在想做的事
you know when it comes to just low-level
你知道什么时候只是低层次的
low-level reflection as opposed to you
与您相反的低反射
know beans and jelly bean components and
了解豆类和软糖成分，以及
so on
依此类推
there's no there's some other things I'd
没有其他的事情
like to be able to inspect as well so
也希望能够进行检查
let's say let's rename this method to
假设我们将此方法重命名为
beans utils and we'll create a new
bean utils，我们将创建一个新的
method here called class utils and the
这里的方法称为类utils，
classic tools method well we will take
经典的工具方法，我们将采取
as a chance to inspect at a lower level
以此为基础进行检查的机会
the sort of runtime state of the type
类型的运行时状态的种类
using reflection and so let's say I want
使用反射，所以说我想要
to get the constructor event type so I
获取构造函数事件类型，所以我
can say class utils
可以说类工具
dot get get the constructor if available
dot get获取构造函数（如果有）
say dental class that class and we have
说那堂课，我们有
no parameters I mean you know we know
没有参数，我是说你知道我们知道
that there's a no argument constructor
没有参数构造函数
so let's say a demo class constructor
所以说一个演示类的构造函数
and this dot log Dutch info log the info
这个点记录荷兰信息记录信息
demo class constructor is this one and
演示类的构造函数就是这个
let's actually use this to create
让我们实际使用它来创建
objects so we'll say new instance and
对象，所以我们将说新实例和
there's no parameters here so okay that
这里没有参数，这样很好
is a restaurant lips will surround this
是餐厅的嘴唇将围绕这
with a try-catch we don't need more than
有了try-catch，我们只需要
one catch method in this case okay and
在这种情况下一种捕获方法可以
exception there we are
例外，我们是
so this is going to give me a back give
所以这会给我回馈
me back up and instance of demo class so
我备份和演示类的实例，所以
let's say log that info we you know new
假设您记录下您知道的新信息
instance demo class demo class
实例演示类演示类
okay let's run this and see what we get
好吧，让我们运行它，看看我们得到了什么
okay there's my new instance object it's
好吧，这是我的新实例对象
it looks as we expected it to right
看起来就像我们期望的那样
there's a simple object that matches the
有一个简单的对象与
you know the makeable looking it's got
你知道它有可制造的外观
an empty array list and it's got there
一个空数组列表，它在那里
it's an invalid state and no exceptions
这是一个无效的状态，没有例外
or thrown so that's gonna be my math
或抛出，那将是我的数学
ability to sort of interact with that
与之互动的能力
type using the Lu we can do this using
使用Lu键入，我们可以使用
the raw class literal definition we
原始类文字定义我们
could certainly get there but there's a
肯定可以到达那里，但是有一个
lot of convenient methods in the classic
经典中的许多便捷方法
tools class so for example determining a
工具类，例如确定
common ancestor between two types the
两种类型之间的共同祖先
chain taking a collection of classes and
连锁店的班级和
turning them into a string you know
把它们变成一个字符串，你知道
finding a class given a certain name a
找到一个给定名字的班级
certain class loader finding all the
某些类加载器找到所有
interfaces in given beam getting the
给定光束中的界面得到
default class photo getting a method etc
默认类照片获取方法等
etc cetera I'd a lot of very convenient
等等等我会很方便的
things happening there now another thing
现在发生的事情另一件事
another way can be type another
另一种方法可以输入另一个
convenient utility class in the in the
中的便捷实用程序类
spring term it is a system property
春季学期是系统属性
utils and the reason we're going to use
utils和我们要使用的原因
this is because we want to be able to
这是因为我们希望能够
talk about the location of certain file
谈论某些文件的位置
so first of all that's been straight
所以首先是直的
system property tales just so we can you
系统属性的故事，所以我们可以
know so we can get a handle on that
知道，所以我们可以解决这个问题
first so here's system property till
首先，这里是系统属性，直到
what we want to do is want to resolve
我们要做的就是解决
user at home and if you know much about
用户在家，如果您了解很多
the way spring boot works is it Maps all
spring boot 的工作原理是它能映射全部
the environment variables all the things
环境变量万物
that are in the environment to know all
在环境中了解所有
the things that are in system to get E&amp;V
系统中获得E＆V的东西
and systems that get properties it puts
和获得属性的系统
them into the spring environment
他们进入春天的环境
abstraction the environment abstractions
抽象环境抽象
just a glorified map of keys and values
只是美化的键和值的映射
and so things like users at home become
所以像家庭用户这样的事情就变成了
injectable or resolvable as a property
可注入或可解决的财产
in the spring application context and
在春季应用程序上下文中
the system proper utils makes it very
系统适当的实用程序使其非常
simple to create you know to resolve
易于创建，您知道要解决
placeholders in a string so here let's
字符串中的占位符，所以让我们
say my home directory is user dot home
说我的主目录是用户dot home
okay that's the string value I'm using
好的，那是我正在使用的字符串值
system
系统
resolved text I'm using system property
我正在使用系统属性的已解析文本
utils and I'm going to resolve I'm going
utils，我要解决，我要去
to log out the resolved
注销解决
texts okay and we say that run this now
文字还可以，我们说现在就运行
we could of course just call system that
我们当然可以调用系统
get property in this case for using at
在这种情况下获取属性以用于
home but it's nice to not have to you
回家，但是没有你真是太好了
know we can use a spring property place
知道我们可以使用弹簧财产的地方
all the resolution syntax within strings
字符串中的所有解析语法
here and get the right result so that's
在这里并获得正确的结果，所以
very convenient now I want to use that
现在非常方便，我想使用
facility to get to create a file and
创建文件的便利和
there's no one to do that do they want a
没有人去做，他们想要一个
bit now now show another way it can be
现在，现在显示另一种可能的方式
typed in the the spring framework which
在Spring Framework 中输入
is the file copy of tools type so a lot
是工具类型的文件副本吗
of folks have ever I'm sure you've
的人曾经相信你
written code that T is the copies and
T是副本的书面代码，
moves around you know bytes from you
到处走动，您就会知道字节
know a to be your leaders in a removes
知道要成为您的领导者
data from one reader to another takes
从一个读者到另一个读者的数据
the data from the reader and turns it
来自阅读器的数据并将其打开
into a stream you know lots of common
到流中，您知道很多共同点
boring soul soul annihilating the boring
无聊的灵魂消灭无聊的灵魂
sort of input and output with anything
任何东西的输入和输出
so in this case I want to look at file
所以在这种情况下，我想看一下文件
copy utils self file copy utils okay
复制utils自己的文件复制utils可以
okay that method there and the in the
好的方法在那里
file copy details what I want to do is I
文件复制详细信息我想做的是我
want to say file copy
想说文件副本
till dot and I'm going to copy the data
直到点，我要复制数据
from a reader into a string
从读者到字符串
alright so let's create a reader here
好吧，让我们在这里创建一个读者
our new file reader and the file reader
我们的新文件阅读器和文件阅读器
is going to expect a file pointer
将期待一个文件指针
naturally okay and so the the way we're
自然可以，所以我们的方式
going to build that file is to going to
要建立该文件是要
use system property tools that resolve
使用系统属性工具来解决
placeholder and I'll just say user dot
占位符，我只说用户点
home and I'll point it to a desktop for
家，我将其指向台式机
Flash content dot txt right so if I look
Flash内容点txt正确，如果我看
at this this is a Java nio Java IO file
这是一个JavaniñoJava IO文件
just a regular JDK type okay come on
只是普通的JDK类型就可以了
good there's my file and the file reader
好的，有我的文件和文件阅读器
is complaining because we it throws an
之所以抱怨是因为我们抛出了
exception so we'll catch that okay you
例外，所以我们会抓住你的
run time exception II and now I want to
运行时异常II，现在我想
get the contents of that file so I'm
得到那个文件的内容，所以我
going to say it is better I'll just say
要说比较好，我只说
I want to put that in there okay
我想把它放在那里
simplify this a bit there we are now I
简化一点，我们现在
want to do is I want to log the content
想做的就是我要记录的内容
so I'll say log contents of file and I
所以我说文件的日志内容
want to use file copy util dot and I
想要使用文件复制效用点和我
want to copy the reader into a string
想要将阅读器复制到字符串中
like so okay so that's using the Java 7
像这样好，所以使用Java 7
auto closable feature you know the try
自动关闭功能，您可以尝试
with feature my ability to to to
具有我的能力
automatically close a closable resource
自动关闭可关闭的资源
things like a following or an input
追随者或输入之类的东西
stream or or whatever and we as we do
流或其他
that we can see that the contents of the
我们可以看到，
file you know it's equal to hello screen
您知道它等于您好屏幕的文件
tips which guides with what what we know
提示，指导我们了解什么
to be true
是真实的
so there's hello spring tips on my
所以我的春季提示
desktop and we can see the results all
桌面，我们可以看到所有结果
right that's very convenient we have the
对，这很方便，我们有
little to other methods there I'm sure
我相信其他方法很少
you can imagine use cases for those as
你可以想象用例
well so final copy utils that's a copy
好吧，最终副本工具就是副本
from one binary to an output file to
从一个二进制文件到一个输出文件
copy from a binary tune-up a stream copy
从二进制优化复制流副本
from one file to another file copy from
从一个文件复制到另一个文件
an input stream to an output stream copy
输入流到输出流副本
to a byte array you know cover file to
到您知道封面文件的字节数组
bite around recovery input streams of
咬伤恢复的输入流
byte array a lot of very convenient you
字节数组很方便你
know data mewling or biting
知道数据窃听或咬人
kind of methods there okay now let's
好的方法，现在让我们
talk about some things that we can do
谈论我们可以做的一些事情
you know to to work with the web tier
您知道要使用网络层
right what we want to do here's one on
正确，我们要做的就是
the work with the read web tier and them
阅读网络层及其相关的工作
you know in
你知道
affect something or to work with
影响某事或与之合作
httpservlet based code okay I'm going to
基于httpservlet的代码好吧，我要去
create a simple rest controller here
在这里创建一个简单的 rest controller
that's why I added the spring boots
这就是为什么我增加了 spring boot
started web endpoint to know the
启动Web端点以了解
relative starters to the applications I
应用程序的相对入门者
want to say public static class simple
想说公共静态类简单
rest controller we don't care about the
rest controller ，我们不在乎
press controller all that much in this
压榨控制器就这么多
case and we're going to have a simple
情况，我们将有一个简单的
endpoint here called high and high it's
端点在这里称为高
just going to avoid a high method and
只是要避免一个高方法
it's gonna be a display me see and
这将是我看到的展示，
pointing right so it's going to return
指向正确，所以它将返回
it's when return is nothing in this case
在这种情况下，返回什么都不是
what it is want to tell spring entity to
要告诉Spring实体做什么
inject the server requests and again I'm
注入服务器请求，我再次
not expecting you to inject us or
不希望您注入我们或
request in fact if you well well with
要求实际上是否很好
the spring MVC code should absolutely
Spring MVC代码应该绝对
never use the HTTP request you shouldn't
永远不要使用不应该使用的HTTP请求
need it I knew there's a lot of
需要它，我知道有很多
facilities in the spring that allow you
春天的设施让您
to get beyond and to not depend upon a
超越和不依赖于
low-level servlet request but if you're
低级Servlet请求，但如果您
writing certainly code is about server
肯定会写关于服务器的代码
components that it can be very useful to
可能非常有用的组件
know that there are you know api's that
知道你知道api是
can make working without that code easy
可以使没有该代码的工作变得容易
even if you're not in spring sort of
即使你不是在春天
environment right so here i'm going to
环境不错，所以我在这里
say i want to get a a parameter let's
说我想获取一个参数让我们
say i want to have a an age parameter ID
说我想拥有年龄参数ID
so I'm going to say that service request
所以我要说那个服务请求
utils dot get into parameter I'm going
utils点进入参数我要
to inject or in pass the request rather
注入或传递请求
and the name of the parameters going to
以及要转到的参数名称
be the age and I'll have a default value
是年龄，我将使用默认值
of one right or maybe 18 right I don't
我不知道一项权利或18项权利
know so let's say that does it you know
知道所以让我们说你知道吗
we can even have a negative value so we
我们甚至可以有一个负值，所以我们
could say give us a negative value so if
可以说给我们一个负值，所以如果
it's you know we'll get a value and if
你知道我们会得到一个价值，如果
it's not something that was entered in
这不是输入的内容
the request and we know that something
的要求，我们知道
is wrong right so here long that info
是错的，所以在这里
age is age you know we can do other
年龄就是您知道我们可以做其他事情的年龄
things here we can find out the web
我们可以在网上找到的东西
servers temporary directory as well so
服务器临时目录也是如此
we can use web utils don't get web get
我们可以使用网络实用工具
temp dear either and this takes a server
temp亲爱的，这需要一台服务器
context and we can get that of course by
上下文，我们当然可以通过
dereferencing it from the HD servant
从HD仆人中取消引用
request like this
这样的要求
and this is actually a Java util file a
这实际上是一个Java util文件
dot IO file and we can confirm that as
点IO文件，我们可以确认为
well so temporary directory for patchy
好吧，临时目录不完整
Tomcat is and pass that there so catch
Tomcat是通过那里的所以
the past okay and we can also if we're
过去还可以，如果我们
in a servlet environment and we're using
在servlet环境中，我们正在使用
spring and this is something you
春天，这就是你
probably don't do in modern code but if
可能在现代代码中没有，但是如果
you've got really really old and you
你真的很老而你
know excruciating the old code it's
知道破坏旧代码是
possible to hoist spring up in a spring
可以在春天升起
application and then an advocate access
申请，然后提倡辩护人进入
beans from component code that doesn't
组件代码中没有的bean
otherwise you know live inside of spring
不然你知道住在春天
so if you if you have servlets and they
因此，如果您有servlet并且它们
want to talk to services that are
想与
managed by spring that that context is
由春天管理，那个上下文是
called a web application context and
称为网络应用上下文
there's a very convenient method here
这里有一个非常方便的方法
request context utils that helps you
请求可以帮助您的上下文工具
find the web application context given a
找到给定的Web应用程序上下文
request and a server sort of servlet
请求和服务器类型的servlet
context in this case you'll need the
在这种情况下，您需要
server context that web application
该Web应用程序的服务器上下文
context is actually an implementation of
上下文实际上是
application context so this is a spring
应用程序上下文，这是一个春天
application context that you can use to
您可以使用的应用程序上下文
now look up you know you references just
现在查找您知道您引用了
like you would in very old screen code
就像您在很旧的屏幕代码中一样
so here I'm actually just asking spring
所以我实际上只是问春天
for a pointer to the environment bean
用于指向环境bean的指针
right the environment object that spring
对那个春天的环境对象
maintains for you and we can use that to
为您维护，我们可以用它来
to whatever I don't get a property here
不管我在这里没有财产
right so I'll get property user dot home
正确，这样我就可以将物业用户点回家
log info web application context
日志信息Web应用程序上下文
resolved property equals hello just log
已解析的属性等于您好，只需登录
that out as well and run that if you run
以及运行，如果您运行
it it's not going to you know we have to
它不是要你知道我们必须
actually now invoke this so I'm going to
实际上现在调用它，所以我要
do is I'm going to I'm going to create a
我要做的是创建一个
web method here that that calls an
在这里调用一个
endpoint so in our clamoring runner
终点，所以在我们喧闹的赛跑者中
we'll just have a web method okay
我们将有一个网络方法好
and I'll just create a simple rest
我将创建一个简单的休息
template R T equals new rest template
模板RT等于新的休息模板
and our users template to get a response
和我们的用户模板以获取响应
or action just to trigger a call to
或仅触发电话的操作
localhost:8080 for such hi and I don't
本地主机：8080这样的喜，我不
really care about the return value here
非常在乎这里的返回值
I just want to call the service and
我只想致电服务，
confirm that when I call the service we
确认当我致电服务时，我们
see on the command line they you know
在命令行上看到他们认识的人
the output for users into lead calls
用户的输出转化为潜在客户
okay so let's see what that looks like
好吧，让我们看看它看起来像什么
okay so the temper the egg is negative
好吧，所以脾气蛋不利
one so we didn't actually submit an age
一个，所以我们实际上没有提交年龄
if we could have though you know the
如果我们可以，尽管您知道
request parameter the temporary
请求参数临时
directory is private var folders ball of
目录是私有var文件夹的
law Tomcat dot whatever right pointing
法律Tomcat点不管正确指向
to work Tomcat localized route and then
工作Tomcat本地化路由，然后
the word application context results
单词应用上下文结果
property equals users Jayla you know
属性等于用户Jayla，您知道
what you saw earlier so again we're
你刚才看到的，所以我们再次
talking to our application we're talking
与我们的应用程序交谈
to our spring services inside of a
到我们的春季服务中
servlet API and certain times a service
Servlet API和某些时间的服务
service code base which is very
服务代码库非常
convenient occur trying to do things
方便尝试做事
inside of a an application okay there's
在应用程序里面好吧
some other conveniences here as well
这里还有其他一些便利
right what I want to do is I want to
对，我想做的就是
look at a sort of low-level sort of
看一种低层次的
low-level perspective I want to take a
我想从一个低层次的角度
low-level perspective to objects that
对对象的低层次透视
are managed by Springs AOP mechanism
由Springs AOP机制管理
right so spring makes it very simple to
对，所以春天使它变得非常简单
introduce business logic into an object
将业务逻辑引入对象
declaratively in a single place
声明性地放在一个地方
especially if you have cutting concerns
特别是如果您有减少顾虑
things like transaction management and
诸如交易管理和
logging and you know auditing whatever
日志记录，您知道审计什么
you whatever these concerns are
你不管这些担心是什么
it's pretty simple to introduce these
介绍这些非常简单
concerns using aspect-oriented
有关使用面向方面的问题
programming with the way we do this at
用我们这样做的方式进行编程
one time the way the springtime work
春天的工作方式
does this for you ultimately is that it
最终为您做到的是
creates a proxy and it can do this a
创建一个代理，它可以做到这一点
couple of different ways if you're just
几种不同的方式，如果你只是
using if you're introducing behavior
在介绍行为时使用
based on an interface into a it's
基于到它的接口
interesting introducing concrete
有趣的介绍混凝土
behavior into a beam of a certain type
行为变成某种类型的光束
of interface then we can use regular JDK
接口，那么我们可以使用常规的JDK
proxies which have been supported for
受支持的代理
for more than a decade in the JDK
在JDK中已经有十多年了
otherwise we have to use something a
否则我们必须使用一些
little bit more sophisticated thing
更复杂的东西
called a engineered proxy so you know
叫做工程代理，所以你知道
being able to introspect and work with
能够自省和与之合作
proxy beam can be very useful in some
代理光束在某些情况下可能非常有用
very obscure
非常晦涩
granted but but still sometimes useful
理所当然，但有时仍然有用
circumstances right so let's introduce a
情况合适，所以让我们介绍一个
simple aspect something that'll that'll
简单的方面
change the behavior of our application
改变我们应用程序的行为
so what we want to do is we want to have
所以我们要做的是
am
上午
a method here on our demo class that's
在我们的演示类上的一种方法是
that's called when the application is in
当应用程序在其中时调用
your science right that was you know
你知道的科学权利
before the beam is put into service
在光束投入使用之前
we're going to have a maybe for method
我们将有一个可能的方法
right here are set up there we go I'll
就在这里设置在那里，我们去
just call this begin there we go
只是叫这开始我们就去
absolutely remember memorable right and
绝对记得难忘的权利，
in the beginning method all I'm going to
在开始的方法中，我要做的就是
do is just log that we're looking right
只是记录我们正在寻找正确的日志
it's a log data info begin and when
这是一个日志数据信息，何时开始
spring starts up this is going to be the
春天开始了，这将是
equivalent of initializing beam so it'll
等效于初始化光束，所以它将
call that method after the applications
在应用程序之后调用该方法
I mean after the beam has been
我的意思是说
constructed up to all the properties
构成所有属性
have been satisfied it be a via the
已经满意，这是通过
constructor or setter methods and that
构造方法或设置方法
what we want to do now it's can aspect
我们现在想做的是可以
that that runs before this particular
在这个特定的之前运行的
method gets called just a trivial aspect
方法被称为琐碎的方面
so I'm gonna create an aspect here of
所以我要在这里创造一个方面
ecstatic class before aspect a simple
欣喜若狂的方面，一个简单的方面
before aspect and I want spring to
之前，我要春天
manage this beam so I have to take turn
处理这个光束，所以我必须轮流
it into a component this is not a
它变成一个组件，这不是一个
stereotype annotation it's more of a
刻板印象注解更像是
quality of other components in spring
春季其他零件的质量
and will create a aspect that gets
并将创造出
executed before the execution of the
在执行之前执行
begin method on any component right so
在任何组件上都可以使用begin方法，因此
we're going to obviously in this case we
在这种情况下，我们显然要
know that it'll only match our our
知道它只会匹配我们的
particular beam our little demo class
特别是我们的小样课程
here but you know I want to have
在这里，但你知道我想拥有
something to work with here so we're
这里有一些需要配合的东西，所以我们
going to say when somebody calls baby
要说什么时候有人打电话给婴儿
for method pass in the the join point
对于方法传递连接点
okay and here when just log dot info
好的，这里只是记录点信息
before and log that info during point
之前并在该点记录该信息
dot two string okay and if that goes as
点两个字符串好吧，如果那样
we expect them we should see that these
我们希望他们，我们应该看到这些
two lines are printed out before before
之前打印了两行
the again call ultimately gets called
再次呼叫最终被呼叫
right so let's see that in action
好的，让我们看看实际情况
just prove into working okay I must have
证明工作就可以了
done something on I didn't introduce the
做了一些我没有介绍的东西
ALP support did I no pointer green tells
我没有绿色指针告诉ALP支持
let's make sure I've activated
确保我已经激活
aspect-oriented prod proxy right a o P
面向方面的产品代理权
proxies nope I still did something wrong
代理不，我还是做错了什么
let's see we have a simple aspect that
让我们看看我们有一个简单的方面
gets run on any begin method and I
在任何begin方法上运行，我
should do that let's get a signature
应该这样做让我们获得签名
and we have a component here called big
我们这里有一个叫做big的组件
genes it looks okay let's see if that
基因看起来还不错，让我们看看
works I think I may have just had a
我想我可能刚刚创作的作品
invalid reference there's no looks like
无效的参考没有看起来像
I've done something silly err non
我做了一些愚蠢的错误
pointer beans Oh
指针豆哦
we have more properties now so there's
我们现在有更多的物业，所以
evidently a property that we are not
显然我们不是一个财产
able to get a reed method for indeed
确实能够获得簧片方法
this is where we introduce the AOP
这是我们介绍AOP的地方
framework we introduced compliant we
我们引入的框架符合我们
introduced some types that get weaved
介绍了一些编织的类型
into our code that aren't obvious unless
进入我们的代码，除非
you're doing sort of low-level
你正在做一些低级的
reflection because the the proxies are
反思，因为代理是
ultimately runtime compatible with the
最终运行时与
types that we expect whether their
我们期望他们的类型
objects have implemented the same
对象已实现相同
contract as the beam that we gave it to
像我们给它的光束一样收缩
modify it to we've but it adds extra
修改它为我们，但它增加了额外的
things as I at the end the day it's all
最后的事情就像我一样
something a specialized class it's a
一些专门的课程
subtype that does some you know whatever
做一些你知道的子类型
it needs to do is to make it look like
它需要做的是使其看起来像
we can choose this behavior without
我们可以选择这种行为而无需
actually modifying the code even though
实际修改代码，即使
ultimately it does so I'm going to go
最终做到了，所以我要走了
ahead and remove this because we're now
继续并删除它，因为我们现在
tripping over some sort of property that
绊倒某种财产，
doesn't have a read nip it might have a
没有读压区，可能有一个
set method instead but it's you know
设置方法，但是你知道
we're not in it to call it okay so when
我们不称它为好，所以当
I do that I am given me see here yeah
我这样做是为了让我看到这里
everything seems to be okay we're it's
一切似乎都很好，我们是
clear that being AOP support is working
清楚获得AOP支持正在起作用
now let's go ahead and inspect that
现在让我们继续检查
let's go ahead and interrogate the
让我们继续审问
status of all this so we're going to use
所有这些的状态，因此我们将使用
the AOP utils and spring here and i'll
AOP实用程序和春天在这里，我会
say then i want to get to class
说然后我想去上课
i want to see if they being here demo
我想看看他们是否在这里演示
class demo and I want to say a opie till
上课示范，我要说一句直到
not to get target class demo class and
不获得目标课程的示范课程和
what this gives me is the the actual
这给我的是实际的
bean the actual type the onion earlier
豆实际类型早些
is the origin type the source type the
源类型是源类型
raw type the site that we put into it
原始键入我们放入其中的网站
and not the realized sub
而不是实现的子
that was created dynamically for us at
是为我们动态创建的
one time so we pass this thing in here
一次，所以我们在这里传递了这个东西
and it will say that the class is target
它会说班是目标
class okay blog type info and then we'll
上课好，博客类型信息，然后我们将
ask it is an AOP proxy also AOP utils a
问它是AOP代理还是AOP utils
is LP proxy there's this and we want to
是LP代理吗，我们想要
do the same for is a generic if it's
如果它是通用的
seeded specialized proxy so again
播种的专业代理，所以再次
knowing the difference is all that
知道差异就是全部
useful but it might be thing we want to
有用，但这可能是我们想要的东西
do so let's see how to do that okay so
这样做，让我们看看如何做到这一点
that it is both a AOP proxy and a cg
它既是AOP代理又是cg
good property in this case that's very
在这种情况下很好的财产
convenient with now we are able to
现在我们可以方便
inspect that now we we went into an
检查一下，现在我们进入了
issue of communites ago that we we were
在我们之前的社区问题
tripping up over a field that was
绊倒在原本是
introduced when we added aspectj proxy
当我们添加Aspectj代理时引入
and we D when were enabled that behavior
我们D何时启用了该行为
the aspect got weaved into a component
方面被编织成一个组件
code and it created a a mess that we
代码，它造成了一个混乱，我们
weren't easily able to understand
不容易理解
because there are fields that are not
因为有些字段不是
visible the types that we're working
可见我们正在工作的类型
with that are present at runtime thanks
与存在于运行时谢谢
to the sort of subtyping they've done in
他们所做的那种亚型
subtyping that happens fantasy so it
发生幻想的子类型，所以它
would be nice to have a way to sort of
有一种方法可以很好地解决
enumerate fields and methods and so on
枚举字段和方法等
so let's next to look at the reflection
所以我们接下来来看一下反射
details inside of spring as well so
春天里面的细节也是如此
where's my am where's my command line
我在哪里，我的命令行在哪里
runner-up here good I'm going to use any
亚军在这里好，我将使用任何
method here call that reflection will
这里的方法调用反射
say reflection utils calling or Spring
说反射实用程序调用或Spring
Framework and they give us so convenient
框架，它们给我们带来了如此方便
that you know several methods that make
你知道几种使
it simple to work with things that are
处理简单的事情很简单
potentially shaky or could cause trouble
可能摇晃或可能引起麻烦
in certain objects right so
在某些物体上，所以
I want to find all the fields in a given
我想找到给定的所有字段
class right so demo class class and it's
上课的权利，所以演示课上课了
going to give me it's going to ask me
要给我它要问我
for a new field call back and a call
进行新的现场回拨和通话
back it's just a callback interface it's
返回它只是一个回调接口
like a template method that gives us a
就像模板方法一样，
field and there I can say log that info
字段，在那里我可以说记录该信息
field equals field that two strings can
字段等于两个字符串可以的字段
of course the Scalia job 8 lambda that's
当然，Scalia工作8 lambda是
I think very convenient we can use the
我认为很方便，我们可以使用
reflection utils as well to find a
反射实用程序以及找到
particular field in our class or demo
我们班级或演示中的特定领域
class type class in this case the field
类类型在这种情况下是类字段
is going to be called list and will then
将被称为列表，然后
have that and that field as a java.lang
将那个和那个字段作为java.lang
reflect field and I can I use this to
反映领域，我可以用它来
you know I think I can inspect it and I
你知道我想我可以检查
can find out information about it so lot
可以找到很多有关它的信息
of that info list to string and I can
该信息列表的字符串，我可以
log that out but this is going to be a
注销，但这将是一个
limited information right so we'll look
信息有限，所以我们来看看
in a second add something called
一秒钟内添加称为
resolvable type which will give us even
可分辨的类型
more information about this about this
关于此的更多信息
field ok so it's a private final mom
好的，这是一个私人最后的妈妈
field is equal to private you know the
字段等于私有，您知道
one field that we found is equal to
我们发现的一个字段等于
private final Java util lists list of
私有最终Java util列表的列表
course and then we when we inspect a
当然，当我们检查一个
particular one we get the same exact
特别是一个，我们得到完全相同的
results I could have done the same kind
结果我本可以做同样的事情
of thing with do with methods right so I
与方法有关的事情，所以我
can say demo class that class method log
可以说该类方法记录的演示类
that info method equals and say method
信息方法等于说方法
done to string and run this
完成字符串并运行它
okay and we can see here that we have a
好的，我们可以在这里看到我们有一个
fair bit more code then we may have been
更多的代码，然后我们可能已经
aware and of course so that's a side
知道，当然这是一面
effect of both the aspectj support as
AspectJ支持的效果为
well as the the Lombok preprocessor of
以及Lombok的预处理器
you know the agent a compile-time
您知道代理是在编译时
processor that's being been introduced
即将推出的处理器
into our code so we get all that for
进入我们的代码，所以我们得到了所有
free right we got all these extra
自由权利，我们得到了所有这些额外的
methods even though we may not be
即使我们可能不是
particularly aware of it so that's very
特别意识到这一点，这非常
convenient we can see all the stuff and
方便，我们可以看到所有的东西和
we can see all that's been added to our
我们可以看到所有已添加到我们的
class and we can you know iterate all
类，我们可以知道所有迭代
the methods in the class as well
类中的方法
now I want to go back to seal this field
现在我想回去封印这个领域
has a generic parameter and so it's in
有一个通用参数，所以它在
order to in order to understand more
为了了解更多
about that I want to use the resolvable
关于我要使用可解析的
type RT I can say resolvable type dot
我可以说RT类型是可解析的点
for field and I can pass in exist primer
现场，我可以通过存在的底漆
here and the RP you know will give me
在这里，你知道的RP会给我
the ability it gives me an ability to
这种能力使我有能力
find out what the genetic parameter or
找出什么遗传参数或
parameters of the particular field are
特定字段的参数是
so in this case they know that it's a
所以在这种情况下，他们知道这是一个
list of maps of certain kinetic
某些动力学图谱列表
parameters so log data in fall RT to
参数，以便将秋季RT中的数据记录到
string like this run the reflection
像这样的字符串运行反射
method
方法
okay and when we we do that we can see
好的，当我们这样做时，我们可以看到
it shows us a Java list Java util map
它向我们展示了一个Java列表Java util映射
java.lang string java.lang object so
java.lang字符串java.lang对象如此
it's aware of the generic types of our
它知道我们的通用类型
instance variable right which is very
实例变量对，这非常
convenient and we can drill into that we
方便，我们可以深入了解
can say give me a generic parameter for
可以说给我一个通用参数
you know get the generics and then we
你知道得到仿制药，然后我们
can give up into a particular generic
可以放弃一个特定的通用名
parameter we can even then resolve it
参数，我们甚至可以解决它
even further we can go or we can keep
更进一步，我们可以走，也可以保持
going we can recursively go down and
我们可以递归下去
find the generic parameters and inspect
找到通用参数并检查
them and so on
他们等等
dynamically right this is very very
动态地对，这非常非常
powerful thing to work with if you have
如果有的话，可以使用的强大功能
generic types in here
这里的通用类型
and your system alright let's see so
和你的系统好吧，让我们看看
today we've looked at we've looked at
今天我们已经看过
the beam util they've looked at class
他们看过的梁工具
util so it's a property till file copy
util，所以它是一个属性，直到文件复制
util web you know some things that we
util Web，您知道一些我们
help you in the web LP support
帮助您获得Web LP支持
reflection support and and these are
反思支持，这些是
just the beginning right there's
刚开始的时候
actually a fair number of other ones
实际上还有很多其他的
that we haven't even had a chance to
我们甚至没有机会
look at here but I think you can you I
看这里，但我想你可以我
think you should have the idea of what's
认为你应该有什么想法
possible right there if you look you're
如果你看起来就在那里
more than likely going to find something
更有可能找到一些东西
that may help you so don't be so quick
可能对您有帮助，所以不要那么快
to to rush out to bring in yet another
赶紧带来另一个
library now that we're discouraging you
现在我们劝阻您
from using some of the lines in some
从一些使用一些行
cases he absolutely should some of these
在某些情况下，他绝对应该
utility classes that I've just shown you
我刚刚向您展示的实用程序类
here are not guaranteed to be stable for
这里不保证稳定
example alright so if you can find some
这个例子很好，所以如果你能找到一些
of the library that is going to make
将要制作的图书馆
that guarantee for you and you're
对你的保证，你就是
willing to carry the extra dependency
愿意承担额外的依赖
that's fine
没关系
right absolutely but if you're just
绝对正确，但如果您只是
looking for some of these convenient
寻找一些方便的
methods you may find that these are art
您可能会发现这些是艺术
in the class path and there they've
在课堂上，他们在那里
already been battle tested they're being
已经经过战斗测试，他们正在
they're being used by components in the
它们被组件中的组件使用
spring framework and a spring ecosystem
Spring Framework 和春季生态系统
for a long time so they're certainly
很长一段时间，所以他们肯定
usable and worthy
有用和值得
hopefully they'll they'll serve you and
希望他们会为您服务，
in in some ways someday and with that
有一天以某种方式
thank you very much for watching and
非常感谢您的观看和
we'll see you next time
下次见
you
您